Hello everyone, I am very happy to be here today to learn and share with you the application of CLO 3D technology in clothing courses.
Yesterday, I listened to the sharing of Mr. Gao and Mr. Luo. In fact, I feel that I have gained a lot.
Because I usually take a course on clothing structure.
From Mr. Gao's sharing of 3D virtual technology and clothing structure courses, I really learned a lot and was deeply inspired.
Maybe we will continue to improve in the future.
Next, I would like to talk about the innovation and practice of our school in digital technology in professional courses.
In the latest McKinsey report, it was pointed out that in 2030, 800 million people will be replaced by machines.
China will face the transformation of the profession.
From this point of view, our country will face the largest-scale change in employment.
As a professional education worker, we must always pay attention to the new trend of industry development,
so that our education can keep up with the pace of the times.
Next, I will mainly talk about the application of digital technology in our school's clothing professional teaching process.
The first is professional accuracy.
Professional accuracy is important for the development of the industry.
In 2035, the key core technology, especially digitalization, networkization, and intelligent development,
has made a breakthrough.
The clothing industry has made new breakthroughs in the new industry, the new model, and the new service.
Design, plating, customization, etc.
The appearance of ODM, product innovation,
has created a new model of soft and fast-reaction supply chain.
Digital technology and the deep integration of industries,
the new industry state,
sharing and manufacturing factories,
will become the standard service of the industrial workers.
Therefore, we have conducted some corporate research and teaching activities many times.
We have also made a lot of thoughts and improvements in the application of digital technology in the course.
In Guangdong province,
our school is located in Guangdong province.
Guangdong province is a major clothing industry.
The development of the clothing industry is also very rapid.
There is a lack of intelligent and information-based talent promotion for corporate transformation and upgrade.
New technology and manufacturing integration is a new model for the future.
There are still more hard workers in Guangdong province.
If you think about it,
some management people who design and design projects every year
will need to recruit at least 8,000 new people.
In Guangdong province,
there are about 7 clothing-related vocational schools.
There are about 33 high-quality vocational schools.
There are about 400 graduates per year in high-quality vocational schools.
There will be a little more in high-quality vocational schools.
On average, there may be about 100 students in each school.
There are also some clothing graduates from various places.
If this is added up,
it will not meet the entire needs of the school.
Therefore,
we still have a hard work area.
There is a lack of talent.
There is also a lack of talent in digitalization technology.
Next, I will talk about the basic situation of our school.
There are three majors in our school's clothing academy.
One is the clothing design and supply industry major.
The other is the clothing and clothing industry major.
There is also a leather design major.
There are three directions in the clothing design and supply industry major.
One is engineering,
marketing,
and needlework.
One of the biggest characteristics of our school is that
there are a lot of people in the clothing industry.
Our school is only in the third grade of high school.
But the total number of students in our school can reach 3,000.
That is to say, there are more than 1,000 graduates per year.
It is the largest clothing industry in Huanan.
It has 33 clothing design senior engineers.
It is a brand demonstration major and a focus major in Guangdong Province.
In general, the school's employment situation is good in recent years.
This is our employment statistics in May of 2023.
Because we have a relatively large number of graduates,
there are about 1,000 graduates per year.
Last year, there were 1,006 graduates.
In May of last year, the number of graduates reached 99.3%.
Of course, some of our students chose to study in a special course.
Then they went to the school to continue their education.
Most of the students went to work.
But we have about 90% of the total number of graduates.
In order to provide high-quality employment for our students,
the teachers in our school are actively learning new techniques and methods
to improve the quality of clothing education and to optimize the development of the industry.
In the course of practical education,
teachers are also actively developing and using digital resources.
The second thing I want to talk about is the construction of digital rich energy creation resources.
First of all, the rise of virtual imaging technology.
It can quickly measure fabric,
design and modify,
implement and present,
and smoothly complete a transition between 3D and 2D print.
In addition, it can carry out some diversified array display design,
such as virtual embroidery, and so on.
The digital technology of clothing
allows us to go from digital platform to style design
to virtual clothing production,
and then audit and modify,
and finally, connect to smart production.
In this way, our design to smart production
is fully digitalized.
Clothing technology is an integral part of our business.
Clothing 3D technology can complete the entire process
of clothing from construction to implementation
through a computer.
It can greatly reduce the error rate of paper samples
by changing the thinking from 2D to 3D.
It can determine the design sample,
and reduce the cost of green environment.
For designers,
the transition from 2D to 3D is more familiar,
and communication with 3D printers is smoother.
Design is more reasonable.
Clothing 3D technology
combines the work of designers, 3D printers,
and sample workers,
reducing the chance of error.
Similarly, 3D virtual technology
has been used by many companies
to achieve a cloud-based fashion
through virtual fashion.
For example, China International Fashion Week
is a new ecosystem
where virtual fashion shows,
virtual clothing shows,
and physical-virtual synchronized marketing
have been transformed into one.
Our school is also based on
the principle of technology integration,
time-lapse integration,
and teaching innovation.
We have built four schools,
one is the Professional Virtual Fashion Training Center,
the Public Virtual Fashion Training Center,
the Virtual Fashion Experience Center,
and the Virtual Fashion Creative Center.
In the Professional Special Fashion Training Center,
we have the Special Fashion Fashion Center
for the fashion industry.
Next, we will introduce
some resources for cooperation development
and application and teaching
of virtual fashion.
Let me introduce them to you.
The first one is
a virtual certification system
designed for the fashion industry.
It can help our students
to participate in some practice fashion shows.
Because we have the exam
of the 1 plus X certificate
for the fashion show,
through this practice,
we can make the certificate pass
relatively high.
The second one is
the virtual certification system
for the fashion static exhibition and show.
This can combine
some design skills
and some virtual shows.
This is one of the
national virtual certification projects.
One of the sub-projects
is a certification resource
for the fashion museum.
After we build this resource,
we will think about the following courses
and will combine them with it.
We have already used it for a while.
There are the clothes of various ethnic groups
and the clothes of two common ethnic groups
in the South China Sea region
and the clothes of Lingnan.
We also have a museum
in the South China Sea region.
For example,
we can do some project teaching
with the class of the fashion history
and the class of women's fashion,
men's fashion,
and the class of men's fashion.
In the class of the fashion history,
there will be various fashion trends.
We will guide our students
to do some digital restoration.
We will put some excellent works
into this museum.
It is also for the students
to do some study.
These are some works of our students.
Although it is not perfect,
there are still some shortcomings,
but I think that through this method,
the learning activity of students
will be higher.
After I come out,
this is a video I recorded in advance.
Let me introduce it to you a little bit.
In addition,
we have two more ethnic clothes.
These two ethnic clothes
are Yao and Zhuang.
In this video,
I will show you
the characteristics of
Yao and Zhuang ethnic clothes
and some of their digital costumes.
We have put them all in this video.
When our students
in the design class
are in the third year of high school,
there is a graduation ceremony.
Before they go out,
we will let them do a study in advance.
In this way,
when they are in the ceremony,
they will have more goals.
These are some of the works of Yao and Zhuang ethnic clothes.
Finally,
we have a Lingnan ethnic clothes.
In the Lingnan ethnic clothes,
we mainly put some of our local,
for example,
Xiangyunsha,
Yuexiu,
and some of the local
characteristics of our local clothes.
One of them is
the clothes of our school,
Chen Yiran.
These are some of the products
of our collaboration with the school.
We will put them in this video.
We will also put some of our students'
excellent design works
in this video.
We will also put some of our students'
awards works in this video.
This is a brief introduction
of our museum.
In the following courses,
we will still use our resources
to let our students
learn professional knowledge better.
Next,
we will talk about
our school's
development,
and cooperation with the school
for a virtual
design.
This is our first virtual
you will have an understanding of the equipment in advance.
In terms of design,
we have modularized all the parts of the shirt and suit.
Students can design the style they want to do
in advance through the selection method,
and then take it to the next course.
This is our group outfit.
Compared to the previous group outfit,
it has one more module.
We will put the process of craftsmanship into it.
The process of craftsmanship will be more detailed.
Students will know how to make it before making it.
In this way, they will be able to complete it quickly
when they do the actual work.
Because our high-level vocational schools
pay more attention to the training of students' skills.
This is the application development of some of the digital resources of our school.
Next, I will talk about the application in our teaching process.
We also carry out some professional reforms in the teaching process.
This is in line with the development of our entire industry.
In terms of professional reform,
we include the reform of the talent training model
and the reform of the course standards.
We also include the requirement of digitalization.
We also have the construction of a digital training room
and a platform.
I have mentioned it above.
In terms of reforming content,
we include practical teaching,
course improvement and professional improvement,
and the collaboration of the faculty and the school,
as well as improving our teaching methods, and so on.
The second is a school-level association.
In terms of teaching at the school,
we will carry out some digitalization of the school.
In terms of teaching at the school, we will carry out some digitalization of the school,
including the education of some system-based digitalized related software,
including the learning of our Kolo 3D modeling design software
and some learning of design processing software,
and we used some co-operational platforms.
We will also include some of this kind of related knowledge
into the marketing courses.
The second one is enterprise production.
This mainly relies on the collaboration of some school-level school,
school, school and school.
And we carry out high-quality professional planning,
and it is very interesting.
such as research and development of artificial intelligence technology,
research and development of technical patents,
and development of our experimental and practical training system, etc.
In terms of talent employment,
we mainly focus on the training of digitalized talents and employment guidance.
Here, we have provided guidance on the training of digitalized talents,
professional certification, and internship employment, etc.
We have also established some industrial universities.
Here, I have listed two typical ones.
One is the Ida Industrial University,
which is co-founded by our local Ida Group,
and the Spring Small Technology Co., Ltd.,
which has established the Spring Small Technology Specialization Institute.
This is mainly for the development of some digitalized talents,
training, and the exchange of employment teams.
The Specialization Institute is mainly digitalized in the field of smart manufacturing.
Next,
these are some projects of our corporate cooperation.
This is a project that we led students to participate in last year.
This project consists of three series of costumes.
The modeling and embroidery videos are all made by our students.
This is a small piece of the final film.
Of course, we cannot produce this scene now.
We may also lead students to learn
how to build some simple scenes
with some third-party software.
These are also some corporate cooperation projects that we have completed.
Next, I would like to talk about
some exploration applications of our teaching teaching methods.
We mainly use this virtual imaging technology
to adopt the modeling,
construction,
and division tasks
to carry out some teaching scenarios for clothing training.
As shown in this picture,
this is a digitalized module in our women's clothing integration course.
Here,
our students will carry out a 3D digitalization design
at the beginning of the design.
Then, after the payment is made,
they will go into production.
Also,
in this 3D digitalization design course,
we will introduce the real task
to use the virtual factory
to identify the equipment,
process preparation,
and material preparation scenarios
to break down the gap between school and school.
This is our 3D,
that is, our CLO 3D course.
Our school is called 3D Clothing Design and Application.
This course,
because we are in the senior stage,
it is a three-year course.
Our professional class time is relatively tight.
At first,
our class was set to 28 students.
Later, it was changed to 32 students.
Now,
if we are students in engineering class,
we may gradually want to add 48 classes.
It's like this.
Because the class is relatively short,
so we can only learn some basic content.
Here,
these are some of our students' works.
We also require students to join their own design
in the class
and then in some of the basics that our teachers have explained.
Basically,
the works that our students have taught us
are basically the same.
Each of them has different styles
and looks are different.
In the initial class,
we mainly talked about a T-shirt,
shirt,
sweater,
pants,
shirt,
and a half-sleeved skirt.
It's probably like this.
There are some of these craft skills in the back.
Many of them are learned by the students themselves
after class.
For example,
in the class,
there are some things
that our teachers can't meet face to face.
I would recommend our students
to study in the official class
on B station.
For example,
the last picture in the back
is a work of a student's homework.
For example,
this is a production of a special school,
Dengguang.
My class teacher didn't talk about it.
This student
went to study by himself.
Of course,
if he or she encounters any problems
in the learning process,
he or she can also
communicate with the teacher at any time.
Next,
this is a class
on the structure of the men's flat surface.
In many cases,
when we learn this class,
our 3D software
is actually not learned.
So,
at this time,
our 3D software
is actually
operated by the teacher
when it is in use.
In addition to Kolo 3D,
we also use other things
in this class.
For example,
this is a 3D intelligent measurement mirror.
This one
can measure the size
by standing on it
and scanning a circle
through this mirror.
It's not the same
as the traditional one.
The data may be a little different,
but I think it's enough
for our work.
The second one
is a digital fabric scanner.
We scan the fabric
in advance here.
It is also a use
for the students
in Kolo 3D
in the back
to use the texture
and line drawing.
In this way,
after the students
finish the board,
they can add the fabric directly.
Then,
they can go in
and see the effect.
These are the three software
that we used
in the class.
In the course
of teaching the teacher,
the application of Kolo 3D software
is mainly
like this.
I have two examples here.
The first one
is that
when we are talking
about specification design,
we have to explain
to the students
how many sizes
should be added.
Why should we add
these sizes?
For example,
I used
the hard disk
in the 3D software
here.
I want to see
what the pressure
is like.
Then,
we can analyze it.
The second example
is that
when we are making
shirts,
some people
may have
a demand
for the uniformity
of the shirt.
For example,
if we want to add the voice.
In the traditional way
of teaching,
we will be
taken to the platform
to teach.
This is very laborious.
Now,
after we have this software,
we are more convenient.
We don't have to
run around
with the platform.
This is
our
financial course.
The financial course
is also
prepared by
our teacher
in advance.
We will
use 3D
to make
the financial work
in advance.
In this way,
it is more intuitive
than the photo.
This is
the e-commerce course.
Because
there are some
photos
in the e-commerce course,
some students
will use
3D software
to directly
do the work.
In fact,
the effect
may be
better than
3D software.
This is also
a project
in our
women's
fashion
course.
It is
a combination
of traditional
culture
and embroidery
with some
students' works.
The last thing
I want to
talk about
is
graduation
design.
Here,
for graduation
design,
our school
has about
1,000 graduates
every year,
so not
every student
has to do
a graduation
essay.
Some students
are in the
orderly class.
For the
students in
the orderly class,
we don't
require them
to complete
the final
task.
We require
them to
adapt
the digital
3D clothing
to their
graduation design.
This is
a work
of a student
in the orderly class.
He made
three sets,
including
the accessories
for graduation
design,
and the
work
for graduation
design.
He made
six sets
in total.
Finally,
he made
an exhibition.
The exhibition
here is
also
because
students
may
not
like
the 3D
software
of the
scene.
In the end,
the scene
is more
flat.
This is
a work
of the
student
in the orderly class.
In the
beginning,
he made
the 3D
clothing first.
This is
a photo
of the
graduation
exhibition.
The
3D
work
is
displayed
at the
top.
The
next
is
the
final
result
of
the
3D work.
The 3D work
is
the
final
result of
the
3D work.
The 3D work
is
the
final
result
of
the
final
result.
The
3D work
is
a
3D
work
of
the
student.
This
is
the
final result
of the
competition
of
the
second
year
of
the
3D
work
and
the
international
student
engineering
training
in
China.
This
is
a
work
of
the
first
national
3D
This student's work won the first place in the first prize.
It's mainly in terms of design.
The other student won the first prize in design.
This is a prize from another teacher
who led a student to participate in a national innovation competition.
She also won an award for cooperating with an enterprise.
What I want to say is that
every year, we have a teaching competition in a professional school.
Our school won the first prize in the national competition for two consecutive years.
In the second year, we won the first prize.
In the third year, we won the second prize.
In these two competitions,
we applied digital technology to the course.
The first one is a project in the design of women's clothing.
We applied the 3D design of women's clothing in the design phase.
The second competition was a class in men's clothing craftsmanship.
But in the development phase of women's clothing,
we also applied the 3D design of women's clothing.
The last one is a QR code in the virtual interview room of our school.
If you are interested,
please take a look at the QR code.
Finally, I will use eight words to explain my sharing.
I hope this kind of technology will be born in the future.
I hope our professional education work will be better and better.
Thank you, everyone. That's all for my sharing.